bridge.edu 2014-05-15

# Privacy Policy

Bridge-Linguatec (“we,” “us” or “our”), provides language immersion courses, teacher training programs, volunteer opportunities, translation and interpretation services, and a variety of other language-related services worldwide. Because our ability to serve you successfully depends on building and maintaining communication with you, we have implemented measures designed to protect the privacy of your personal information, as described in our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy governs your interaction with our website and your use of our online services. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use or other published guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information gathered through our website about you without your permission.

Please note that we review and may change our privacy practices from time to time. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. You may determine whether we have changed our Privacy Policy since you last reviewed it by checking the date of adoption set forth below. To contact us about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy or to raise any other issue, please contact us via our contact information provided on the bottom of each page of the website.

### The information we gather

We gather two types of information about users of our website:

**1\. Non-personally identifiable information:** When you visit our website, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the website were visited, the order in which they were visited and which hyperlinks were “clicked.” Collecting such information involves the logging of the IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to our website. If your IP address is dynamically assigned by your internet service provider, or ISP, we can identify your ISP and determine the geographic location of your point of connectivity.

We also use “cookies” (i.e. small text files placed on your computer hard drive by our servers) to help us determine the type of content and sites to which you link, the length of time you spend at any particular area of our website, which services you use and which products you purchase. Essentially, cookies are your identification card. Cookies can only be read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently and to personalize your experience at our website. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.

**2\. Personally identifiable information:** We may collect personally identifiable information about you through various means. In certain areas of our website – for example, when registering with us, signing our guestbook, emailing us to purchase products or services, filling out an online application, or using the “Request Information” page – you may directly provide us with personally identifiable information (including, for example, first and last name, school and work experience, date and country of birth, country of citizenship, references , interests, personal preferences, street address, email address, telephone number, fax number and if applicable, credit card information) of you and others. In addition, if you provide your personally identifiable information to our affiliates or business partners, they may share such information with us (subject to their privacy policies). If your IP address is statically assigned by your ISP, we may also collect personally identifiable information about you through our logging of your IP address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (i.e. minors younger than 13 years of age). If you are a minor, we request that you have a parent or guardian read this policy and request any information you are seeking from us on your behalf. By providing personally identifiable information to us, you represent that the person whose information you are providing is not a minor.

#### Linking of non-personally identifiable information we gather with your personally identifiable information

Once you have registered with our website, we may be able to link your personal information to the non-personally identifiable information we have collected through the use of cookies as described above. For example, once you register, we could see what type of content and sites you have viewed, the length of time you have spent at any particular area of our website and which products and services you have used or purchased in the past and from that point on, track that information with respect to your future visits to our website.

### How we use (and do not use) the information we gather

Please take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways we use the information that we gather. Keep in mind that we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, such as our affiliates and business partners for which we have links on our website or third party providers, including the manner in which they use information received from us or from you directly or independently. Please know that we have a third party provider who supplies a shopping cart solution for our website, and collects personally-identifiable information including billing information. Any information that you provide to this third party provider via our website or to any other third party providers via our website, will be subject to the third party provider’s privacy policy. If we receive your personally identifiable information from a third party, we will use such information in accordance with our agreements with such third party, but do not assume any obligation to you. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for privacy practices of third parties or the content of their websites, including such sites’ use of any information collected when visitors to our website click through links to those sites. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites and third parties. If you feel that any third party, including any provider, affiliate or business partner of ours, is improperly collecting or using information about you, you may wish to contact such third party.

**1\. Non-personally identifiable information:** We use non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of our website. We may provide statistical information based on this data to current and potential affiliates and business partners. We may also use the aggregate data to inform our affiliates and business partners as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their websites. If we sell or transfer some or all of our assets or our company, we may sell or transfer non-personally identifiable information as part of such transaction.

**2\. Personally identifiable information:** You can always choose not to provide your personally identifiable information to us by not registering with us, signing our guestbook, emailing us to purchase products or services, filling out an online application, using the “Request Information” page, subscribing to our mailing or notification lists or otherwise providing such information to us or to our affiliates or other business partners. If you provide your personally identifiable information to us or to our affiliates or other business partners with your consent that they share your information with companies like ours, we may use it to email or send you information regarding our company and the products and services that we offer, or to consider qualifications or enroll you in a program. If you do not wish to receive such information from us, please see “Unsubscribing from our Marketing Distribution Lists” below. We will use your personally identifiable information to provide the products and services that you request.

We will not provide your personally identifiable information to third parties outside of our affiliates and business partners, except to third parties who may assist us in processing orders and sending information to you and as required by law or to enforce our rights. In addition, if we sell or transfer some or all of our assets or our company, we may sell or transfer personally identifiable information as part of such transaction.

We reserve the right to release information contained within our access logs concerning any visitor when we reasonably believe that such visitor has violated our Terms of Use or other published guidelines or has participated in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order. We also reserve the right to release such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities and may report any suspected illegal activity to appropriate authorities for investigation or prosecution.

### Updating your personally identifiable information

If you have provided us with your personally identifiable information through our website, you may update such information by logging in to our website and submitting your new information or by contacting us via the contact information at the bottom of each page of our website.

### Unsuscribing from our marketing distribution lists

If you would like to unsubscribe from our marketing distribution lists, please contact us via the contact information at the bottom of each page of our website. In addition, if we send you an email, you can unsubscribe by responding to the email with a “Remove” request per the instructions noted in the email. We will comply with your request within ten business days. Keep in mind, however, that residual information will remain within our databases, access logs and other records. We will not use the residual information for commercial purposes, but reserve the right to re-contact former customers or users of our website from time to time in compliance with applicable laws.

Adopted July 15, 2005
